The National Utility Authority meeting before Tuesday, February 25th,
the invocation by Ms. K. Bowman.
My God, our guest in down upon those who hold office in the city,
the spirit of wisdom and charity and justice at my steadfast purpose.
They may faithfully serve and their children up the well-being of all the peace through Jesus Christ our Lord.
Amen.
Let you lead to the flag of the United States of America and choose the Republic for which it sounds.
One nation under God, in the midst of the liturgy of justice for all.
Greg, on public uniterious and unskilled we have none.
Five, five, claims.
Motion.
Second.
Five.
Jones.
I, Gordon, I, EastF.
Five.
Madam of six.
minutes from the February 4th regular meeting.
Question.
Second.
I'm Rethel.
Hi.
Don's.
There were seven.
Action out of master service agreement with owned formerly Anderson Engineering for Engineering Services.
Yes, board.
This is for owned Anderson Engineering for the engineering.
To do our city engineering stuff for us.
They do a lot of different projects for us.
You know, they do testing for the streets.
You know, a survey workforce.
They do, you know, surveys on our properties that we bought.
You know, make sure it's check.
I mean, they do a slew of different things for us.
We just have an on-call contract with them that we have paid them an hourly rate.
And this is just three new it.
So.
So do we pay them a monthly fee?
No.
We paid them just like an out.
We paid them an hourly rate.
Kind of like we do our attorneys and everything else.
Anything you want to add there?
It took all your sunshine?
Sorry.
I'm going to.
I'm going to entertain a motion.
I'll make motion.
Second.
Jones.
Hi.
Orange.
Number eight.
Ash down on board to bid.
Revis Walter.
Well, and construction for contract.
DS RF project number.
Two zero zero eight one three dash.
Two.
New space.
We said.
And I would like to point on to the administrative board that this is the first of our large project that we received you green on so this is like
The actual us actually doing the construction so I mean, you know, there'll be many more of these coming about but this is like
This is the first of our
We related to the
We had the one out that we had to do a large super parol
This is the different location but this would actually help us in the future if something like that happens we'd have other areas that we could store water to pump water into the town
We were done in like inventory for these or probably not right on the six hundred dollars
Well, not this is just this is actually the building
Yeah, we're just one half right there on the corner
We bought that you know a few years. We bought that property from ROTA
Is that the triangle?
Yes, sir. I'll get that's the triangle
Motion to approve
Second
Hi
Jones
I
On
Hi
I'm not so you're explain that here
We had
We had a pretty good community all year
And the bar
Again
Yeah, so it's 50% of the amount of the $500
So the number of the numbers is going to be ruined
Yep
Yeah, motion to approve
Second
He's said
All right
Sorry. I'm going to read you that
What's going on?
Hi
Jones
I
Barnes
Hi
Thank you guys great job
That's exciting
Any other business
So sorry, I didn't mean I'm going to talk to
I'm going to sign it
I'm going to move
Go for it
Other business that has a reason since the Posting of the agenda
And staff reports
Trusty community announcements
I have number three
Our team is meeting we'll be continuing from the council chambers and we convened in the staffer to discuss the executive session of the completion of the regular meeting of the C.
My Miss City Council.